Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/alexandra-belanger-6ab911117 (LinkedIn)

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) French (Native or Bilingual)

Alexandra Belanger

Bilingual Paralegal/Law Clerk
Toronto

Summary

Alexandra Belanger has been a bilingual Paralegal since 2008 working in all domains of the law in both Quebec and Ontario, including: Employment Law, Transportation Law, Corporate Law and Immigration Law.

In her current role, Alexandra provides assistance to in-house counsel and other professionals regarding the preparation of supply agreements, distribution agreements, marketing and sponsorship agreements.

In addition, Alexandra is responsible for the preparation of various employment settlement documents and facilitates communications between Human Resources and terminated employees in the event of dispute.

Alexandra also has experience completing research assignments on the CanLII legal database as well as on the sites of the Quebec Transport Commission (transport permit and exploitation rights), the Office of Consumer Protection, the Registrar of companies and the Canadian Intellectual Property Office.

Experience

The Coca-Cola Company
7 years 11 months
Senor Bilingual Law Clerk
May 2013 - Present (7 years 11 months)
Toronto, Canada Area

Employee Relations Business Partner July 2016 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Heenan Blaikie Legal Assistant August 2012 - May 2013 (10 months)

Toronto

Heenan Blaikie S.E.N.C.R.L. Paralegal

January 2011 - August 2012 (1 year 8 months)

Education

College Bart

Paralegal, Legal Assistant/Paralegal · (2008)

Activity

03/21/2021, Kelley Jones-Bellucci (she/her) added candidate to VCNA- Law Clerk

03/21/2021, Message sent by Kelley Jones-Bellucci (she/her)